(this.webpackJsonpmiretoapp=this.webpackJsonpmiretoapp||[]).push([[0],{24:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"question":"How can you access the state of a component from inside of a member function?","no":1,"answers":[{"key":1,"value":"this.getState()","correct":"false"},{"key":2,"value":"this.prototype.stateValue","correct":"false"},{"key":3,"value":"this.state","correct":"true"},{"key":4,"value":"this.values","correct":"false"}]},{"question":"Inline styling in React can be done as:","no":2,"answers":[{"key":1,"value":"style:{{}}","correct":"false"},{"key":2,"value":"style:{}","correct":"true"},{"key":3,"value":"style:\'\'","correct":"false"},{"key":4,"value":"All","correct":"false"}]},{"question":"For classless component we use?","no":3,"answers":[{"key":1,"value":"functions","correct":"true"},{"key":2,"value":"classes","correct":"false"},{"key":3,"value":"JSX","correct":"false"},{"key":4,"value":"None","correct":"false"}]},{"question":"Which method in a React Component is called after the component is rendered for the first time?","no":4,"answers":[{"key":1,"value":"componentDidUpdate","correct":"false"},{"key":2,"value":"componentDidMount","correct":"true"},{"key":3,"value":"componentMounted","correct":"false"},{"key":4,"value":"componentUpdated","correct":"false"}]},{"question":"What happens when you call setState() inside render() method?","no":5,"answers":[{"key":1,"value":"Repetitive output appears on the screen","correct":"false"},{"key":2,"value":"Stack overflow error","correct":"true"},{"key":3,"value":"Duplicate key error","correct":"false"},{"key":4,"value":"Nothing happens. Life goes on!","correct":"false"}]},{"question":"What is ReactJS?","no":6,"answers":[{"key":1,"value":"Server side Framework","correct":"false"},{"key":2,"value":"User-interface framework","correct":"false"},{"key":3,"value":"Both","correct":"true"}]},{"question":"Props are __________ into other components ","no":7,"answers":[{"key":1,"value":"Injected","correct":"false"},{"key":2,"value":"Methods","correct":"true"},{"key":3,"value":"Both above","correct":"false"},{"key":4,"value":"None","correct":"false"}]},{"question":"Which of the following API is a MUST for every ReactJS component?  ","no":8,"answers":[{"key":1,"value":"getInitialState","correct":"false"},{"key":2,"value":"render","correct":"false"},{"key":3,"value":"renderComponent","correct":"true"},{"key":4,"value":"None","correct":"false"}]},{"question":"At the highest level, React components have lifecycle events that fall into ","no":9,"answers":[{"key":1,"value":"Initialization","correct":"false"},{"key":2,"value":"State/Property Updates","correct":"false"},{"key":3,"value":"Destruction","correct":"false"},{"key":4,"value":"All of these","correct":"true"}]},{"question":"What is a react.js in MVC? ","no":10,"answers":[{"key":1,"value":"Controller","correct":"true"},{"key":2,"value":"Middleware","correct":"false"},{"key":3,"value":"Model","correct":"false"},{"key":4,"value":"Router","correct":"false"}]}]')},26:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(39)},31:function(e,t,a){},32:function(e,t,a){},39:function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var n=a(0),r=a.n(n),c=a(21),s=a.n(c),o=(a(31),a(11)),l=a(12),i=a(15),u=a(14),m=a(13),d=(a(32),a(9)),v=a(10),h=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var t=Object(m.a)(a);function a(){return Object(o.a)(this,a),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(l.a)(a,[{key:"render",value:function(){return r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("div",{id:"index-banner",className:"parallax-container"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"section no-pad-bot"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},r.a.createElement("br",null),r.a.createElement("h1",{className:"header center"},"Mi Reto"),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"row text-center"},r.a.createElement("h5",{className:"header col"},"Responda estas 10 preguntas b\xe1sicas de reacci\xf3n con 10 puntos cada una.")),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"row"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"col text-center"},r.a.createElement(d.b,{to:"/running",className:"btn btn-secondary"},"Empezar")))))))}}]),a}(n.Component),f=a(40),p=a(41),y=a(42),k=a(43),E=a(44),b=a(45),w=a(46),N=a(24),q=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var t=Object(m.a)(a);function a(e){var n;return Object(o.a)(this,a),(n=t.call(this,e)).state={ques:1,score:0,isLoaded:!1,items:[],answ:[]},n}return Object(l.a)(a,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){this.setState({isLoaded:!0,items:N})}},{key:"checkAnswer",value:function(e){"true"===e?this.setState((function(e){return{ques:e.ques+1,score:e.score+1}})):this.setState((function(e){return{ques:e.ques+1}}))}},{key:"renderQuestions",value:function(){var e=this;return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"m-4"},r.a.createElement(f.a,null,r.a.createElement(p.a,null,r.a.createElement(y.a,{className:"text-success"},this.state.items[this.state.ques-1].question)),this.state.items[this.state.ques-1].answers.map((function(t,a){return r.a.createElement(p.a,{onClick:function(){return e.checkAnswer(t.correct)},key:a},r.a.createElement(k.a,null,t.value))}))),r.a.createElement("br",null),r.a.createElement(d.b,{to:"/",className:"btn btn-primary"},"Ir a la p\xe1gina principal"),r.a.createElement("br",null))}},{key:"renderFinish",value:function(){var e=this;return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"mt-4"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"text-left pl-4"},this.state.items.map((function(t,a){return r.a.createElement("div",{key:a},r.a.createElement("p",{className:"text-primary m-0"},t.no,".-  ",t.question),e.state.items[a].answers.map((function(e,t){return"true"===e.correct?r.a.createElement("p",{className:"text-secondary m-1",style:{fontSize:"1.0rem"},key:t},"R.-    ",e.value):""})))}))),r.a.createElement(d.b,{to:"/",className:"btn btn-warning mt-3"},"Iniciar prueba nuevamente"))}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this.state.items.length;return this.state.isLoaded?r.a.createElement("div",{className:"p-3 m-4"},r.a.createElement("h3",{className:"header center teal-text text-lighten-2"},"Mi Reto"),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"row text-white"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"col-md-6 "},r.a.createElement(E.a,{body:!0,color:"primary"},r.a.createElement(b.a,null,"Numero de Pregunta"),r.a.createElement(w.a,null,this.state.ques))),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"col-md-6"},r.a.createElement(E.a,{body:!0,color:"secondary"},r.a.createElement(b.a,null,"Puntuaci\xf3n"),r.a.createElement(w.a,null,this.state.ques<=e?"-":this.state.score)))),this.state.ques<=e?this.renderQuestions():this.renderFinish()):r.a.createElement("div",null)}}]),a}(n.Component),S=function(e){return r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("div",{className:"row"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"col"},r.a.createElement(E.a,{body:!0,outline:!0,color:"secondary"},r.a.createElement(b.a,null,"Score"),r.a.createElement(w.a,null,e.score)))),r.a.createElement(d.b,{to:"/",className:"btn btn-secondary"},"Get Started"))},g=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var t=Object(m.a)(a);function a(e){var n;return Object(o.a)(this,a),(n=t.call(this,e)).state={disp:"start",score:0},n.handleState=n.handleState.bind(Object(i.a)(n)),n}return Object(l.a)(a,[{key:"handleState",value:function(e){var t=arguments.length>1&&void 0!==arguments[1]?arguments[1]:0;this.setState({disp:e,score:t})}},{key:"render",value:function(){return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},r.a.createElement(d.a,{basename:"".concat("/miretoweb","/")},r.a.createElement(v.c,null,r.a.createElement(v.a,{exact:!0,path:"/",component:h}),r.a.createElement(v.a,{exact:!0,path:"/running",component:q}),r.a.createElement(v.a,{exact:!0,path:"/finish",component:S}))))}}]),a}(n.Component);Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));a(38);s.a.render(r.a.createElement(r.a.StrictMode,null,r.a.createElement(g,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()})).catch((function(e){console.error(e.message)}))}},[[26,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.dd31a9cf.chunk.js.map